--- Testing Dashboard Stats ---
Total Vacancies: 7
Active Vacancies: 5
Talent Pool Size: 6
Total Potential Matches: 5

--- Testing Vacancy Match Counts ---
Job: SENIOR ACCOUNTS EXECUTIVE (SENIOR ACCOUNTS EXECUTIVE) -> Matches: 0
Job: Senior Software Developer (Development) -> Matches: 0
Job: REGIONAL MARKETING MANAGER (REGIONAL MARKETING MANAGER) -> Matches: 0
Job: SALES COORDINATOR (SALES COORDINATOR) -> Matches: 0
Job: SENIOR ELECTRICAL ENGINEER (SENIOR ELECTRICAL ENGINEER) -> Matches: 0
